{
    "1": [
        {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How many hulls are there on a catamaran?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How many states in the USA begin with the letter M?",
        "answer": 8
        },
        {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In tennis, how high is the net in feet?",
        "answer": 3
        },
        {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How many children did Queen Victoria have?",
        "answer": 9
        },
        {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How many moons does Mars have?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "How many suns does Kepler-16b have?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How many holes are there in a bowling ball?",
        "answer": 3
        },
        {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How many continents are there on Earth?",
        "answer": 7
        },
        {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "How many children does Queen Elizabeth II have?",
        "answer": 4
        },
        {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "How many wives did Henry VIII have?",
        "answer": 6
        },
        {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "How many studio albums did Stoner Roses release?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "How many cities are there in Scotland?",
        "answer": 7
        },
        {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "What is the atomic number of carbon?",
        "answer": 6
        },
        {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "What is π to 0d.p?",
        "answer": 3
        },
        {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
        "answer": 3
        },
        {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "How many Karamazov brothers are there?",
        "answer": 4
        },
        {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "How many chambers in a human heart are there?",
        "answer": 4
        },
        {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "How many vowels are in word 'vowel'?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "How many consonants are in a word 'consonant'?",
        "answer": 6
        },
        {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Binary code consists of 0s and _s ?",
        "answer": 1
        },
        {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "How many stars in flag of Australia are there?",
        "answer": 6
        },
        {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "What is the PH of pure water?",
        "answer": 7
        },
        {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "4444 divided by 4444?",
        "answer": 1
        },
        {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "How many colours does the rainbow consist of?",
        "answer": 7
        },
        {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "How many countries does UK share land border with?",
        "answer": 1
        },
        {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "How many angles does triangle have?",
        "answer": 3
        },
        {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "How many angles does pentagon have?",
        "answer": 5
        },
        {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "How many people can engage in a duel?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "How many zeros does million have?",
        "answer": 6
        },
        {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "What’s a third prime number?",
        "answer": 5
        },
        {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Mourinho a Special...?",
        "answer": 1
        },
        {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "The ... little piggies",
        "answer": 3
        },
        {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "What’s a fourth even number?",
        "answer": 8
        },
        {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "What number does infinity symbol resembles the most?",
        "answer": 8
        },
        {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "How many languages do bilinguals speak?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "How many hemispheres does human brain have?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "At least how many siblings does a single a twin have?",
        "answer": 1
        },
        {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "In the Hobbit, what ring does Bilbo find?",
        "answer": 1
        },
        {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "how many does it take to dance the tango?",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "There is a rock band called U_?",
        "answer": 2
        }
    
    ],
    "2": [
        {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How many keys does a full-sized piano have?",
        "answer": 88
        },
        {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How many labours did Hercules perform?",
        "answer": 12
        },
        {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "How many inches are there in a cubit?",
        "answer": 18
        },
        {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How many shillings in a Guinea?",
        "answer": 21
        },
        {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How many numbers are there on a bingo board?",
        "answer": 90
        },
        {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What do the Roman numeral L represent?",
        "answer": 50
        },
        {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How many squares on a checkers board?",
        "answer": 64
        },
        {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How many black squares on a chess-board?",
        "answer": 32
        },
        {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What is the minimum legal age to buy alcohol in the UK?",
        "answer": 18
        },
        {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is the minimum age for jury service in the UK?",
        "answer": 18
        },
        {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "What is the highest-value note issued as British currency?",
        "answer": 50
        },
        {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "How many jurors are Scottish trials populated by?",
        "answer": 15
        },
        {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "97 - 72 + 1 =?",
        "answer": 26
        },
        {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "How many people have walked on the moon?",
        "answer": 12
        },
        {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "How many legs does a shrimp have?",
        "answer": 10
        },
        {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "How many hours in a day?",
        "answer": 24
        },
        {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "How many minutes in an hour?",
        "answer": 60
        },
        {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "How many times zones does Russia stretch over?",
        "answer": 11
        },
        {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "How many teeth does an adult human have?",
        "answer": 32
        },
        {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "How many chromosomes does the average human have?",
        "answer": 23
        },
        {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "How many toes does a cat have?",
        "answer": 18
        },
        {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "How many discovered moons does Saturn have?",
        "answer": 82
        },
        {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "What percent of the total surface area of Earth is land?",
        "answer": 29
        },
        {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "How many letters in the word ‘presbyterianism’?",
        "answer": 15
        },
        {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "How many states are there in the US?",
        "answer": 50
        },
        {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "How many cities are there in the UK?",
        "answer": 69
        },
        {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "What is the meaning of life, the universe, and everything?",
        "answer": 42
        },
        {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "How many countries does EU consist of ?",
        "answer": 27
        },
        {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "How many countries does Commonwealth consist of ?",
        "answer": 54
        },
        {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "4 x 4 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": 64
        },
        {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "How many zodiac signs are there ?",
        "answer": 12
        },
        {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "How many bones does human skull consist of?",
        "answer": 22
        },
        {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "How many hours a day do elephants spend feeding?",
        "answer": 18
        },
        {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "What’s the highest number of pH scale?",
        "answer": 14
        },
        {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "What’s 0 Celsius degrees in Farenheit?",
        "answer": 32
        },
        {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "How many letters are there in English alphabet?",
        "answer": 26
        },
        {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "What’s 50% of 100?",
        "answer": 50
        },
        {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "How many stars are there in flag of EU?",
        "answer": 12
        },
        {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "How many Boroughs does London consist of?",
        "answer": 32
        },
        {
        "id": 40,
        "question":  "What do all the keypad numbers add up to ?",
        "answer": 45
        }
    ],
    "3": [
        {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How many acres fit in the square mile?",
        "answer": 640
        },
        {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What number did Sherlock Holmes live at?",
        "answer": 221
        },
        {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In total, how many dots in a standard domino set are there",
        "answer": 168
        },
        {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How many bones in adult Human body are there",
        "answer": 206
        },
        {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How long did 100 year war last for?",
        "answer": 116
        },
        {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "How many Earth days does one day on Venus last for?",
        "answer": 243
        },
        {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How many pennies in a pre-decimal pound?",
        "answer": 240
        },
        {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "In meters, What’s the minimum height of a munro?",
        "answer": 914
        },
        {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "How many Munros are there in Scotland?",
        "answer": 282
        },
        {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What’s the land speed record in mph?",
        "answer": 763
        },
        {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "How many MPs sit in the House of Commons?",
        "answer": 650
        },
        {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "What is the straight line distance from Land’s End to John o’ Groats in miles?",
        "answer": 603
        },
        {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "in kilometers, how long is the River Thames?",
        "answer": 346
        },
        {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "How old was the oldest person ever recorded?",
        "answer": 122
        },
        {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "In centimeters, how tall was Andre the Giant?",
        "answer": 224
        },
        {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "How many days did the shortest serving British PM serve for?",
        "answer": 119
        },
        {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "How many countries are there in the world?",
        "answer": 195
        },
        {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "How many countries does United Nations consist of ?",
        "answer": 193
        },
        {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "How many Spartan solders fought in Battle of Thermopylae ?",
        "answer": 300
        },
        {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "How many years has Poland lost its independence for ?",
        "answer": 123
        },
        {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "At what negative temperature does oxygen become liquid?",
        "answer": 183
        },
        {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "How many years does it take Pluto to orbit the sun?",
        "answer": 248
        },
        {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "How many years does it take Neptune to orbit the sun?",
        "answer": 165
        },
        {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "What’s the number of the beast divided by 6?",
        "answer": "111"
        },
        {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "What’s UK’s Emergency phone number?",
        "answer": "999"
        },
        {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "What’s the sum of hexagon’s interior angles?",
        "answer": 720
        },
        {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "110 x 3 + 33 - 3 = ?",
        "answer": 330
        },
        {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "In the LOTR how old is Bilbo at his party?",
        "answer": 111
        },
        {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "What's the highest number before 651 and then divided by 2",
        "answer": 325
        },
        {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "What numbers lucky number indicates jackpot?",
        "answer": 777
        },
        {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "What's the quarter of a thousand?",
        "answer": 250
        },
        {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "What’s the highest-value single Euro note?",
        "answer": 500
        },
        {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "What number am I thinking of?",
        "answer": 650
        },
        {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "What’s first three-digit-long prime number?",
        "answer": 101
        },
        {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Four times(seven times ten) = ?",
        "answer": 280
        },
        {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "How old was the oldest animal ever recorded?",
        "answer": 405
        },
        {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "What is the Statue's of Liberty shoe size?",
        "answer": 879
        },
        {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "How many beers did André the Giant drink in 6 hours?",
        "answer": 119
        },
        {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "How many Whiskies did James Bond drink in the original Fleming’s books?",
        "answer": 101
        },
        {
            "id":40,
            "question": "How many countries have been invaded by the British?",
            "answer": 171
        }
    ],    
    "4": [
        {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "When was the battle of Stamford Bridge fought?",
        "answer": 1066
        },
        {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What year did the Great fire of London happen?",
        "answer": 1666
        },
        {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What year did Yuri Gagarin go to space?",
        "answer": 1961
        },
        {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What year was Lady Ada Lovelace, The first programmer born",
        "answer": 1815
        },
        {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "When was the first national flag flown in Denmark?",
        "answer": 1478
        },
        {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "When was King Louis XVI killed?",
        "answer": 1793
        },
        {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What year was the first electric guitar sold?",
        "answer": 1932
        },
        {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "When was the first computer game created?",
        "answer": 1947
        },
        {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "When were the first Winter Olympics held?",
        "answer": 1924
        },
        {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "In kilometers, what’s diameter of the moon?",
        "answer": 3474
        },
        {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "In meters, what’s max. depth of the Atlantic Ocean?",
        "answer": 8486
        },
        {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "In meters, how tall is Mount Everest ?",
        "answer": 8849
        },
        {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "When was the Battle of Hastings?",
        "answer": 1066
        },
        {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "How many feet in a mile?",
        "answer": 5280
        },
        {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "How many seats does  UK parliament consist of",
        "answer": 1440
        },
        {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "5555 - 1111 = ?",
        "answer": 4444
        },
        {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "_ _ _ _: A Space Odyssey (movie)?",
        "answer": 2001
        },
        {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "When was Faraday born?",
        "answer": 1791
        },
        {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "What temperature does Tungsten melt at?",
        "answer": 3410
        },
        {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "What is the melting point of diamond?",
        "answer": 3550
        },
        {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "What’s Roman MMXXI in numbers ?",
        "answer": 2021
        },
        {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "How many 1000s are there in 1 million?",
        "answer": 1000
        },
        {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "How many millions in 1 billion?",
        "answer": 1000
        },
        {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "How many minutes are there in a day?",
        "answer": 1440
        },
        {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "What number comes right before ten thousand?",
        "answer": 9999
        },
        {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "When was Golf made illegal?",
        "answer": 1457
        },
        {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "What year did London Olympics take place in?",
        "answer": 2012
        },
        {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "In kilometers, what's the diameter of Mars",
        "answer": 6752
        },
        {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "In million km, what is the closest Pluto gets to the sun?",
        "answer": 4437
        },
        {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "if 1 = dash and 0 = dot what's morse for letter 'Z'?",
        "answer": 1100
        },
        {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "What’s 55 hectolitres in litres?",
        "answer": 5500
        },
        {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Highest 4-digit number minus lowest 4-digit number = ?",
        "answer": 8999
        },
        {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "What’s the highest four digit number?",
        "answer": 9999
        },
        {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "What would number 9999 turned upside down end up being?",
        "answer": 6666
        },
        {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "How far from the surface is the deepest cave found in metres?",
        "answer": 2200
        },
        {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "How high is the highest point in Europe in metres?",
        "answer": 5642
        },
        {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "How deep is the Indian Ocean in the deepest point in metres?",
        "answer": 7450
        },
        {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "On average, how deep is the Pacific Ocean in metres?",
        "answer": 4280
        },
        {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "How long is the longest river in North America in Km?",
        "answer": 5970
        },
        {
        "id": 40,
        "question":"How tall is Mount McKinley in Alaska in meters?",
        "answer": 6194
        }
    ]
}